Guide to the Tim Smith Collection on The Saint MSS.418
Fales Library and Special Collections
Tim Smith Collection on The Saint
1980-2014
1981-1988
Fales Library and Special Collections
Smith, Timothy Hartley
MSS.418
21 Linear Feet in 18 tall manuscript boxes, two oversize folders, two flat file folders, one manuscript box, four box binders, and three large boxes
992 Sound_Disc--Vinyl
4 CDs
200.82 Megabytes in 233 computer files
The Saint was a gay superclub in the East Village neighborhood of Manhattan, New York, open between 1980 and 1988. The club was owned by Bruce Mailman, an entrepreneur who also owned the New St. Marks Baths in the East Village, and designed by architect Charles Terrell. The Saint was initially a private membership nightclub, eventually allowing non-members to attend on certain nights. After the club closed in 1988, it continued as The Saint At Large, holding events at other nightclubs in Manhattan. The Tim Smith Collection on The Saint contains material collected by Smith during his time as a member (1981-1988) and throughout the existence of The Saint At Large. The collection contains print ephemera housed in scrapbooks, digitized ephemera, photographs, and writings, as well as almost 1000 sound recordings on disc.
Conditions Governing Access
The sound recordings on disc are not available for playback. Researchers may view an item's original container. The print and digitized materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Timothy Hartley Smith, 2014. The accession number associated with this gift is 2014.418.
Historical Note
The Saint was a gay superclub in the East Village neighborhood of Manhattan, New York, open between 1980 and 1988. The club was owned by Bruce Mailman, an entrepreneur who also owned the New St. Marks Baths in the East Village, and was designed by architect Charles Terrell. During its first five years, The Saint was a private membership nightclub and was open seasonally, from Labor Day to mid-June. In its sixth year, it was open year round and held events open to non-members. In addition to the regular Saturday and Sunday dance nights, there were themed and holiday events, including the annual Black Party.
The Saint was a multi-level superclub, known primarily for its 4800 square foot, circular dance floor which was topped with an aluminum dome, 1500 lights, a Graebar sound system, and a Spitz Space System that shone stars and constellations onto the dome. Mailman would change the decor of the club each year and would hold weekly themed events which required extensive decoration of the entire club. There was a core group of DJs and lighting designers and operators, with occasional guests. The regular DJs included Shaun Buchanan, George Cadenas, Michael Fierman, Michael Jorba, Robbie Leslie, Howard Merritt, Chuck Parsons, Terry Sherman, and Sharon White; lighting designers and operators included Mark Ackerman and Richard Tucker. The staff and members were almost entirely white men, with a handful of women holding memberships.
As the club opened in the early days of the AIDS crisis and was open during its height, many of its staff and members were affected. In attempts to keep the club a financial success, Mailman opened the once private club to non-members, opened year round rather than seasonally, and opened extra nights during the week, in addition to Saturday and Sunday nights. Despite these changes, The Saint could not sustain its initial level of success and Mailman decided to sell the building in 1988. After the closing of The Saint in the East Village, Mailman continued to hold events at other nightclubs in Manhattan under the name The Saint At Large.
Scope and Contents
The Tim Smith Collection on The Saint contains print ephemera housed in scrapbooks, digital ephemera, photographs, subject files, and writings about the club, as well as sound recordings of music played at the club. The collection contains material collected by Smith during his time as a member (1981-1988) and throughout the existence of The Saint At Large (1988-ongoing). The print material includes scrapbooks arranged by season containing newsletters, membership cards, fliers, receipts for dues, and Smith's correspondence with club management, as well as posters. Other material includes locker tags and matchbooks from The Saint, and turntables and a DJ mixer acquired by Smith in the 1990s. The fliers include club rules and membership and event information. The posters document events at The Saint and The Saint At Large, including the annual Black Party, Halloween and Christmas parties at The Saint, and special guests. The collection also contains clippings from print and online sources, full periodicals with articles on The Saint, and the club's newsletter, Stardust. Digital materials include subject files compiled by Smith with digitized and born-digital photographs of events at The Saint and The Saint At Large, Saint members and DJs, and the Spitz Space System used at The Saint; lists of music played at The Saint and The Saint At Large; writings about the club by former members and staff; and ephemera from The Saint, the New St. Marks Baths, and the Trippin' On The Moon dance parties inspired by The Saint. The sound recordings include compilations of crowd favorites on CD and a collection of almost 1000 sound recordings on disc. The latter were compiled by Smith and include singles and complete albums of music played at The Saint and The Saint At Large, including disco, pop, dance, and R&B.
Appraisal
MP3 versions of the music and digital scans of the print material in the collection were deaccessioned as they were duplicative.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Advance notice is required for the use of computer records. Original physical digital media is restricted. An access terminal for born-digital materials in the collection is available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Researchers may view an item's original container and/or carrier, but the physical carriers themselves are not available for use because of preservation concerns.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in alphabetical order by format of material. The sound recordings on disc are arranged in the order in which they were received, in rough alphabetical order by artist.
Disco music.; Gay discotheques -- New York (State) -- New York.; Popular music -- 1971-1980.; Popular music -- 1981-1990.; Gay business enterprises -- New York (State) -- New York; Gay men -- United States -- Social life and customs.; Nightclubs -- New York (State) -- New York.; Sound recordings; New wave music.; Phonograph records.; Record covers.; Posters.; Photographs.; Popular music -- 1991-2000.; The Saint (New York, N.Y.)
- Locker tags, 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Matchbooks, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Music equipment, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1, Box 23, Box 24, Box 25)
- Posters, 1980-2006 (Box Shared Fales 001, Folder 9, Box Shared Fales 004, Folder 1-4, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 5)
- Scrapbooks, 1980-2014 (Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box Shared Fales 001, Folder 8, Box 26, Box 1, Folder 4-12, Box Shared Fales 004, Folder 1)
- Sound recordings, 2005, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Sound recordings on disc, 1973-2000, undated
  - Cry Wolf -- A-Ha, 1986 (Box 5)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    12" Single 45 RPM
  - Take On Me -- A-Ha, 1985 (Box 5)
  - The Sun Always Shines On TV -- A-Ha, 1985 (Box 5)
  - The Sun Always Shines On TV -- A-Ha, 1985 (Box 5)
  - The Sun Always Shines On TV (Extended) -- A-Ha, 1985 (Box 5)
  - The Sun Always Shines On TV (Extended) -- A-Ha, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Dancing Queen -- ABBA, 1976 (Box 5)
    7" Single 45 RPM
  - The Visitors -- ABBA, 1981 (Box 5)
    12" Album 33 RPM
  - Happy New Year (Album Version) -- ABBA, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Lay All Your Love On Me -- ABBA, 1980 (Box 5)
    12" Single 33 RPM
  - Lay All Your Love On Me (A Raul Dance Mix) -- ABBA, 1980 (Box 5)
    12" Disconet 33 RPM
  - On And On And On -- ABBA, 1980 (Box 5)
  - The Visitors -- ABBA, 1981 (Box 5)
  - Take My Body -- Ackerman, Tracy, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Absolutely Immune -- Act, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Absolutely Immune -- Act, 1987 (Box 5)
  - I Can't Escape From You -- Act, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Snobbery & Decay -- Act, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Circle Of One -- Adams, Oleta, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Rhythm Of Life -- Adams, Oleta, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Send My Heart (Across The Sea Mix) -- Adventures, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Playing With Fire -- Age of Chance, Undated (Box 5)
  - Number One -- Aida, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Fly To Me -- Aleph, Undated (Box 5)
  - I Think We're Alone Now / Will You Love Me Tomorrow -- Allan, Scott, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Letter From My Heart -- Allen, Steve, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Tears Run Rings -- Almond, Marc, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Forever Young -- Alphaville, 1984 (Box 5)
  - If There's Love -- Amant, 1978 (Box 5)
  - Sexual (Funk Vocal) -- Amber, 1998 (Box 5)
  - I'm Alive -- American Fade, 1983 (Box 5)
  - Love Of My Own -- Anders, Thomas, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Soldier -- Anders, Thomas, 1989 (Box 5)
  - He's All I Want (Trance Vocal) -- Angelmoon, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Touch & Go -- Any Trouble, 1983 (Box 5)
  - O Fortuna (House) -- Apotheosis, 1992 (Box 5)
  - Only -- Aquanote, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Found A Cure -- Ashford & Simpson, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Fire To Ice -- Associates, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Fire To Ice -- Associates, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Forever In The Shadows -- Associates, 1980 (Box 5)
  - Take Me To The Girl -- Associates, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Those First Impressions -- Associates, 1984 (Box 5)
  - What Have I Got To Lose -- Astaire, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Together Forever -- Astley, Rick, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Whenever You Need Somebody -- Astley, Rick, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Whenever You Need Somebody -- Astley, Rick, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Whenever You Need Somebody -- Astley, Rick, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Whenever You Need Somebody -- Astley, Rick, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Interview picture disk -- Astley, Rick, Undated (Box 5)
    12" Single
  - Special Love -- Attack, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Let's Go Round Again -- Average White Band, 1980 (Box 5)
  - The Night -- Azul Y Negro, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Love Shack (12" Remix) -- B-52's, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Come Back And Stay -- Bad Boys Blue, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Hungry For Love -- Bad Boys Blue, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Sweet Love -- Baker, Anita, 1986 (Box 5)
  - I Heard A Rumor (House) -- Bananarama, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Trick Of The Night -- Bananarama, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Venus (Extended) -- Bananarama, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Can't You Feel My Heart Beat -- Barry, Claudja, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Love For The Sake Of Love -- Barry, Claudja, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Trippin' On The Moon -- Barry, Claudja, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Work Me Over -- Barry, Claudja, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Whisper To A Scream -- Barry, Claudja with Bobby Orlando, 1985 (Box 6)
  - This Is My Life -- Bassey, Shirley, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Strangers In The Night -- Bauman, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Too Much In Love -- Bazar, Thereza, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Daydream -- Beagle Music, 1982 (Box 6)
  - The Big Hurt -- Bear Essence, 1983 (Box 6)
  - The Big Hurt -- Bear Essence, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Make That Feeling Come Again/Ah-Do It -- Beautiful Bend, 1978 (Box 6)
  - After The Fall -- Beechman, Laurie, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Theme From Blue Thunder -- Beepers, 1983 (Box 6)
  - You Got The Love -- Belle, Regina, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Seclusion -- Benson, Shawn, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Caught In The Act -- Bentley, Earlene, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Living My Own Life -- Bentley, Earlene, 1984 (Box 6)
  - The Boys Come To Town -- Bentley, Earlene, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Dancing In Berlin -- Berlin, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Don't Get Serious -- Bern, Jacqui, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Smooth -- Bianco, Matt, 1986 (Box 6)
    12" Album 45 RPM
  - Yeh Yeh -- Bianco, Matt, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Honey Be Good -- Bible, The, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Mahalia -- Bible, The, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Heroes -- Big Ben Tribe, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Heroes -- Big Ben Tribe, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Blame It On The Boogie -- Big Fun, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Nobody's Business -- Billie, Undated (Box 6)
    12" Single 44 RPM
  - Wonderful Life -- Black, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Everybody Everybody -- Black Box, 1990 (Box 6)
  - Fantasy -- Black Box, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Fantasy -- Black Box, 1989 (Box 6)
  - Ride On Time -- Black Box, 1989 (Box 6)
  - That's Love That It Is -- Blancmange, 1983 (Box 6)
  - That's Love That It Is -- Blancmange, 1983 (Box 6)
  - That's Love That It Is -- Blancmange, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Shame -- Blase, B., Undated (Box 6)
  - Rapture -- Blondie, 1980 (Box 6)
  - Party Time -- Blow, Kurtis, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Spanish Lullaby -- Blue, 1994 (Box 6)
  - Oxygene -- Blue August Project, 1987 (Box 6)
  - My Bed Is Too Big -- Blue System, 1988 (Box 6)
  - House Of The Rising Sun -- Bona-Riah, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Love And Devotion -- Bow, Michael, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Got To Give Into Love -- Boyer, Bonnie, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Land of Make Believe -- Boys From Brazil, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Can't Take My Eyes Off Of You -- Boystown Gang, 1982 (Box 6)
  - Just Can't Help Believing -- Boystown Gang, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Remember Me-Ain't No Mountain High Enough -- Boystown Gang, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Dance Trance Medley -- Boystown Gang, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Yester-Me, Yester-You Yesterday -- Boystown Gang, 1984 (Box 6)
  - You're The One -- Boystown Gang, 1981 (Box 6)
  - Loving Is Really My Game -- Brainstorm, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Shattered Glass -- Branigan, Laura, 1987 (Box 6)
    7" 45 RPM
  - Solitaire -- Branigan, Laura, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Gloria -- Branigan, Laura, 1982 (Box 6)
  - I'm Not The Only One -- Branigan, Laura, 1983 (Box 6)
  - Satisfaction -- Branigan, Laura, 1984 (Box 6)
  - Self-Control -- Branigan, Laura, 1984 (Box 7)
  - The Lucky One -- Branigan, Laura, 1984 (Box 7)
  - You're Makin' Me High -- Braxton, Toni, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Don't Tell Me Lies (Dance Version) -- Breathe, 1986 (Box 7)
  - How Can I Fall? -- Breathe, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Sing Sing Sing -- Broads, The, 1983 (Box 7)
  - I Love The Nightlife (Disco Round) ('87 Med Mix) -- Bridges, Alicia, 1987 (Box 7)
  - I Love The Nightlife (Disco Round) ('87 Med Mix) -- Bridges, Alicia, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Smalltown Boy -- Bronski Beat, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Smalltown Boy -- Bronski Beat, 1984 (Box 7)
  - He Ain't No Competition...(Extended) -- Brother Beyond, 1988 (Box 7)
  - The Harder I Try -- Brother Beyond, 1988 (Box 7)
  - The Harder I Try -- Brother Beyond, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Party -- Brown, Julius, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Black Leather -- Brown, Miquel, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Close To Perfection -- Brown, Miquel, 1987 (Box 7)
  - Footprints In The Sand -- Brown, Miquel, 1987 (Box 7)
  - He's A Saint, He's A Sinner -- Brown, Miquel, 1984 (Box 7)
  - So Many Men So Little Time -- Brown, Miquel, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Baby Gets High -- Brown, Peter, Undated (Box 7)
  - I Specialize In Love -- Brown, Sharon, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Flashdance What A Feeling -- Cara, Irene, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Gonna Make you Sweat -- C & C Music Factory, 1990 (Box 7)
  - I Specialize In Love (Steven Von Blau/Mark Styles Mix) -- Brown, Sharon, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Sing Sing Sing (DX) -- Calello Orchestra, Charlie, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Love Is A Sheild -- Camouflage, 1989 (Box 7)
  - One Fine Day -- Camouflage, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Love Is A Sheild -- Camouflage, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Suspicious Love -- Camouflage, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Love Is A Sheild (Us Orbit Mix) -- Camouflage, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Strawberry Fields Forever -- Candy Flip, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Maana -- Capuchino, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Flashdance What A Feeling -- Cara, Irene, 1983 (Box 7)
  - The Dream (Hold On To Your Dream) (Dance Remix) -- Cara, Irene, 1983 (Box 7)
  - I Get Weak -- Carlisle, Belinda, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Mad About You -- Carlisle, Belinda, 1986 (Box 7)
  - Was That All It Was -- Carne, Jean, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Invitation To Dance (Vocal Dance Mix) -- Carnes, Kim, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Voyeur -- Carnes, Kim, 1982 (Box 7)
  - You Make My Heart Beat Faster (And That's All That Matters) (Dance Mix) -- Carnes, Kim, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Angel Of Night -- Casablanca, Undated (Box 7)
  - I'm Free -- Celi Bee, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Call Me Tonight -- Cerrone, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Call Me Tonight -- Cerrone, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Cerrone's Paradise -- Cerrone, Undated (Box 7)
  - Supernature -- Cerrone, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Supernature -- Cerrone, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Trippin' On The Moon -- Cerrone, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Searching -- Change, 1980 (Box 7)
  - Il Veliero (Love Is On The Rocks) -- Chaplin Band, The, Undated (Box 7)
  - Got To Get To You -- Charade, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Mellow Lovin' (Remix) -- Cheeks, Judy, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Hold The Line -- Chester, Undated (Box 7)
  - Dance Dance Dance -- Chic, 1977 (Box 7)
  - Christian -- China Crisis, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Wishful Thinking (Old Gold) -- China Crisis, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Wishful Thinking (Virgin) -- China Crisis, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Working With Fire And Steel -- China Crisis, 1983 (Box 7)
  - Working With Fire And Steel -- China Crisis, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Working With Fire and Steel -- China Crisis, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Downtown -- Clark, Petula, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Give Me Just A Little More Time -- Clemmons, Angela, 1982 (Box 8)
  - I Just Wanna Wanna -- Clifford, Linda, 1979 (Box 8)
  - If My Friends Could See Me Now -- Clifford, Linda, Undated (Box 8)
  - If My Friends Could See Me Now -- Clifford, Linda, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Just Around The Corner -- Cock Robin, 1987 (Box 8)
  - The Promise You Made -- Cock Robin, 1985 (Box 8)
  - When You're Heart Is Weak -- Cock Robin, 1985 (Box 8)
  - People Hold On -- Cold Cut featuring Lisa Stansfield, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Dangerous -- Cole, Natalie, 1985 (Box 8)
  - The Late Mistake (Dance Version) -- Comateens, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Never Can Say Goodbye, Undated (Box 8)
  - Don't Leave Me This Way -- Communards, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Never Can Say Goodbye -- Communards, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Never Can Say Goodbye (Sao Paulo Mix) -- Communards, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Tomorrow -- Communards, 1987 (Box 8)
  - You Are My World -- Communards, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Romeo & Juliet -- Constandinos, Alec R., Undated (Box 8)
  - Romeo & Juliet -- Constandinos, Alec R., Undated (Box 8)
  - Megatron Man -- Cowley, Patrick, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Menergy -- Cowley, Patrick, 1981 (Box 8)
  - Mind Warp -- Cowley, Patrick, 1982 (Box 8)
  - My Man -- Cruisin' Gang, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Back To You -- Crystal In The Pink, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Der Erdbeermund -- Culture Beat, 1989 (Box 8)
  - Without Your Love -- Cut Glass, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Without Your Love -- Cut Glass, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Alive With Love -- Cut Glass, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Without Your Love -- Cut Glass, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Without Your Love -- Cut Glass, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Alive With Love -- Cut Glass, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Without Your Love (Yellow Vinyl) -- Cut Glass, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Keep On -- D Train, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Metropolis-Legend Of Babe (Club Mix) -- djdado, Undated (Box 8)
  - Love In The Shadows -- Daily, E.G., 1985 (Box 8)
  - Mind Over Matter -- Daily, E.G., 1987 (Box 8)
  - Casanova -- Dandy, 1989 (Box 8)
  - More More More -- Daryl, 1988 (Box 8)
  - More More More -- Daryl, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Lucky Tonight -- Dash, Sarah, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Shattered Dreams -- Datchler, Clark, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Sahara Night -- David, F.R., 1986 (Box 8)
  - Sahara Night -- David, F.R., 1986 (Box 8)
  - Ain't That Enough For You -- Davis, John and The Monster Orchestra, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Ain't That Enough For You -- Davis, John and The Monster Orchestra, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Love Magic -- Davis, John and The Monster Orchestra, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Love Magic -- Davis, John and The Monster Orchestra, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Ain't Nothing Gonna Keep Me From You -- De Sario, Teri, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Real Gone Kid -- Deacon Blue, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Real Gone Kid -- Deacon Blue, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Maybe (We Should Call It A Day) -- Dean, Hazel, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Searchin' (I Gotta Find A Man) -- Dean, Hazel, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Who's Leaving Who -- Dean, Hazel, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Jealous Love -- Dean, Hazell, 1984 (Box 8)
  - All This Love -- DeBarge, 1982 (Box 8)
  - Good Beat -- Dee Lite, 1991 (Box 9)
  - Good Beat -- Dee Lite, 1991 (Box 9)
  - How Do You Say Love (Pal Joey Mix) -- Dee Lite, Undated (Box 9)
  - What Is Love -- Dee Lite, 1990 (Box 9)
  - What Is Love -- Dee Lite, 1990 (Box 9)
  - What Is Love -- Dee Lite, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Menhungry -- Dee, Maxine, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Feel The Need -- Detroit Emeralds, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Walkin! -- Dhuo, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Hot Butterfly -- Diamond, Gregg, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Shake Me Up -- Dilcher, Cheryl, 1979 (Box 9)
  - In Spirit -- Dilemma, 1996 (Box 9)
  - Over And Over -- Disco Circus, 1981 (Box 9)
  - Night Rider -- Dodson, Venus, 1979 (Box 9)
  - It's Nature's Way -- Dollar, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Too Many Broken Hearts -- Donovan, Jason, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Can He Find Another One (A Jim Burgess Mix) -- Double Discovery (Boris Midney), 1982 (Box 9)
  - Please Don't Go (Club Mix) -- Double You ?, 1992 (Box 9)
  - Take Off Your Makeup -- Dozier, Lamont, 1973 (Box 9)
  - Love Parade -- Dream Academy, 1985 (Box 9)
  - The Love Parade -- Dream Academy, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Telefone (Long Distance Love Affair) -- Easton, Sheena, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Walk Away Satisfied -- Zino featuring Jayne Edwards, 1985 (Box 9)
  - Beat Of My Heart -- Edwards, Mike, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Talking With Myself -- Electribe 101, 1990 (Box 9)
  - Getting Away With It -- Electronic, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Getting Away With It -- Electronic, Undated (Box 9)
  - Getting Away With It -- Electronic, Undated (Box 9)
  - Carillon -- Eller, Dan, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Love Pains -- Elliman, Yvonne, 1982 (Box 9)
  - Love Pains -- Elliman, Yvonne, 1982 (Box 9)
  - My Loleatta -- Ellis "D", 1987 (Box 9)
  - Best Of My Love -- Emotions, 1977 (Box 9)
  - Rejoice -- Emotions, 1977 (Box 9)
  - First, Last-For Everything -- Endgames, 1977 (Box 9)
  - A Little Respect (Extended Version) -- Erasure, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Victim of Love -- Erasure, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Blue Savannah -- Erasure, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Blue Savannah (Der Deutsche Mix) -- Erasure, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Blue Savannah (Out Of The Blue Mix) -- Erasure, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Blue Savannah (Test Pressing) -- Erasure, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Star (Trafalmadore Mix) -- Erasure, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Star (Trafalmadore Mix) -- Erasure, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Stop -- Erasure, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Stop -- Erasure, 1988 (Box 9)
  - Rhythm Is Gonna Get You (Special 12" Dance Mix) -- Estefan, Gloria, 2000 (Box 9)
  - 17 Again (Peter Rauhofer Mix) -- Eurythmics, 1999 (Box 9)
  - Don't Ask Me Why -- Eurythmics, 1989 (Box 9)
  - Don't Ask Me Why -- Eurythmics, 1989 (Box 9)
  - The First Cut -- Eurythmics, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Sexcrime -- Eurythmics, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Love Is A Stranger -- Eurythmics, 1983 (Box 9)
  - Here Comes The Rain Again -- Eurythmics, 1983 (Box 10)
  - I Need A Man Shame -- Eurythmics, 1987 (Box 10)
  - When Tomorrow Comes -- Eurythmics, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Sexcrime -- Eurythmics, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Grown Up Girls -- Eurythmics, 1985 (Box 10)
    12" Hot Tracks 33 RPM
  - Here Comes The Rain Again -- Eurythmics, Undated (Box 10)
  - Love Is A Stranger (Obsession Mix) -- Eurythmics, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Right By Your Side -- Eurythmics, Undated (Box 10)
  - Sweet Dreams (Are Made of This) -- Eurythmics, 1982 (Box 10)
  - Paint A Rumour -- Eurythmics, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Paint A Rumour -- Eurythmics, 1984 (Box 10)
  - There Must Be An Angel -- Eurythmics, Undated (Box 10)
  - When Tomorrow Comes (Extended Version) -- Eurythmics, 1986 (Box 10)
  - When Tomorrow Comes (Extended Version) -- Eurythmics, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Who's That Girl -- Eurythmics, 1983 (Box 10)
  - You Hurt Me -- Eurythmics, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Your Time Will Come -- Eurythmics, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Sisters Are Doin' It For Themselves -- Eurythmics and Aretha Franklin, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Alive With Love -- Fabrique, Tina, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Haven't Stopped Dancing Yet -- Faces, Undated (Box 10)
  - Savin' Myself -- Fachin, Eria, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Savin' Myself (Blaster Mix) -- Fachin, Eria, 1986 (Box 10)